Guide to the Tim Dlugos Papers MSS.087
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Realia
  - Clipboard used at Roosevelt Hospital, undated (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Birthday book, undated (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Glasses, undated (Box 5, Folder 196)
- Oversize - Series IV: Readings, reviews, periodical contributions
  - Subseries A: Readings
    - Beyond Baroque Center Readings, undated (Box 8, Folder 197)
    - Little Caesar Press, undated (Box 8, Folder 198)
    - Other People's Readings, undated (Box 8, Folder 199)
- Accretion 1998 Series I: Correspondence
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 200)
- Accretion 1998 Series II: Manuscripts
  - Subseries A: Book projects
    - Entre Nous (fragment), undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - Je suis Americano., undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Subseries B: Poetry manuscripts
    - Drafts, undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 203)
    - Miscellaneous., undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Subseries C: Other Writings
    - Poetry., undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - Prose., undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - Notepad., undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 207)
- Accretion 1998 Series III: Biographical Information
  - Subseries A: General biographical material
    - Miscellaneous notes., undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 208)
- Accretion 1998 - Series IV: Readings, reviews, periodical contributions
  - Subseries A: Readings and press information.
    - Other peoples' readings., undated; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Subseries B: Interviews and reviews
    - Reviews of Dlugos' books., 1979-1983; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Subseries D: Contributions to periodicals
    - American Artist, 1985 Apr.; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - American Letters & Commentary. No 2, Fall 1989; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Anglican Theological Review. Vol 73, No 3, Summer 1981; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - Art & Understanding, Fall 1991; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - Arts Magazine. Vol 58, No 5, 1984 Jan.; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - Barney. Nos 1, 4, 1981, 1984; 31142040616636 (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - Bird: a fly-by-night Journal of D.C. Poets, 1974; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 217)
    - Bingo Chow. #3, Fall 1978; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 218)
    - The Body Politic. Nos 22, 24, 1976 Feb.; 1976 June; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 219)
    - Brooklyn Review. Nos 6-8, undated; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - Christopher Street. Vol 1, nos 7-8; Vol 3, no3; Vol 4 no 6, 12; Vol 5, no 12; Vol 7, no 3, 1977-1983; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 221)
    - Coda: Poets and Writers Newsletter. Vol 3, no 4; Vol 4, no 2, 1976 Apr., 1976 Dec.; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 222)
    - D.C. Gazette. Vol 15,no 4, 1974 Apr.; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 223)
    - Daily News, 1985 Mar. 10; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 224)
    - Four Quarters. Vol XXV, No 1, Fall 1975; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 225)
    - The Gay Blade., 1975 Apr.; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 226)
    - Gay Sunshine. Nos 13, 24, 33/34, 1975-1977; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 227)
    - GPU News. Vol 9, No 2, 1979 Nov.; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 228)
    - Grimoire (Student Arts Publication at La Salle College), 1970-1989; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - Hanging Loose. No 23, Summer 1974; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - Hot Water Review., 1976; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - JANAAD, Fall 1970; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - Little Caesar. No 10, 1980; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - Mag City. No 6, 1979; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - Margins. No 20, 1975 May; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - Mass Transit: a Magazine of D.C. Poets. Nos 1,3, 1973-1974; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - New York Native. Nos 3, 20, 30, 1981-1982; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - New Yorker., 1991 June 10, 1991 July 29; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - The Painted Bride Quarterly. Vol 1, No 3, Summer 1974; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - Paris Review. No 102, 1987; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Paris Revie. No 115, 1990; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - Phoebe: the George Mason Review. Vol 3, Nos 1,2, 1973-1974; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Poetry Project Newsletter. No 81, 1981 Mar.; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - The Public Citizen. No 1, 1976; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - Record (Buffalo State College). Vol 83, No 45, 1980 Apr. 18; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - Santa Monica Review., Spring 1992; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Shiny International. Nos 4,6, 1988, 1991; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Talisman (Hunter College), Winter 1986; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Theaters. No 5, 1975 Mar./Apr.; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - The Washington Blade Review of Books., 1983 Nov. 11; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - The Washington Post Book World., 1977 Nov. 6; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - The Washington Review. Vol 5, No 3; Vol 8, No 4; Vol 14, No 2, 1979,1982,1988; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Washington Review of Arts. Vol 1, No 1; Vol 2, Nos 1-3, 1975-1976; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - ZZZ, 1974, 1977; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Subseries F: Source Materials
    - Esquire, 1976 May; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - The Kennedys -- America's Royal Family., 1962; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - National Review, 1986 Sept. 12; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - New Republic, 1967 Nov. 7; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1986; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - Newsweek, 1984 Dec. 31; 31142040616644 (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - Scrapbook on Dwight Eisenhower (Box 9, Folder 261)